Finding Aid for the Larry Gelbart Papers PASC.0022
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Projects
  - Television Projects
    - MOOSE (Stage/Television Project) - 2/27-3/8/68, 41 p., incl. outline "Loose Moose", 10 p. & typed script, 20 p. - Handwritten outline for teleplay, 5/26/70, 6 p., typed 8pgs. & 6 p. - Synopsis, 1970. (Box 155, Folder 8)
      2/27-3/8/68, 41 p., incl. outline "Loose Moose", 10 p. & typed script, 20 p. - Handwritten outline for teleplay, 5/26/70, 6 p., typed 8pgs. & 6 p. - Synopsis, 1970.
    - MR. & MRS. - Pilot script by Larry Gelbart (Box 143, Folder 1)
      First draft, n.d., 36 p. - Draft, 09/01/70, 47 p. - Draft, 09/04/70, 44 p.
    - MR. & MRS. - SOLO FOR FOUR HANDS (Box 143, Folder 2)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Draft, 09/09/70, 43 p.
    - MR. & MRS. - Television project notes (Box 143, Folder 3)
      No date. Typed and handwritten, includes revision pages.
    - MY BUDDY - Television project comedy series for Buddy Hackett by Larry Gelbart. (Box 167, Folder 2)
      Draft, no date, 48 p. - Draft, no date, 51 p.
    - MY WIVES, JANE - Scripts for pilot episode written by Larry Gelbart (Box 49, Folder 3)
      First draft, September 25, 1970. - Revised November 1970. - final draft, December 11, 1970. - Additional revised pages.
    - NAM - Idea for a Limited Television Series by Larry Gelbart (Box 155, Folder 5)
      July 30, 1976, 2 pages ms and 2 pages typed. With Writers Guild registration.
    - NETWORK - Articles ( 6 items) (Box 180, Folder 9)
      Regarding production, restarting of the television branch of MGM/UA, hiring of Larry Gelbart as producer, etc. Articles dated January 1996. Most are printouts from AOL.
    - NETWORK - Casting lists for series (Box 180, Folder 10)
      Lists were compiled by Gary M. Zuckerbrod Casting Co. Lists dated April, 1996. 8 items.
    - NETWORK - Correspondence (6 items) (Box 180, Folder 11)
      1996. Profit breakdown, n.d. Cover page for pilot episode, 3/21/96.
    - NETWORK - Pilot (Box 188, Folder 1)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Based on the screenplay by Paddy Chayefsky. First draft. March 1, 1996. 54 pages. 3 copies.
    - NETWORK - Pilot (Box 188, Folder 2)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Based on the screenplay by Paddy Chayefsky. Revised first draft. March 7, 1996. 33 pages. - Handwritten notes for act one.
    - NETWORK - Pilot (Box 188, Folder 3)
      Scripts: One copy is marked "For George, with love, L.G." Dated March 21, 1996. 32 pages. 2 copies.
    - NETWORK - Pilot (Box 188, Folder 4)
      Script. No title page. Marked "3/1/96." 43 pages.
    - NETWORK - Pilot (Box 188, Folder 5)
      Scripts (2 copies): No title pages, no dates. - Annotated with 33 pages. - Annotated with 30 pages.
    - NETWORK - Pilot (Box 188, Folder 6)
      Revision pages. February 22, 1996 (12 pages). - November 28, 1996 (2 pages).
    - NETWORK - Screenplay by Paddy Chayefsky (Box 188, Folder 7)
      MGM/UA, 1976. Dated May 15, 1975. Annotated. 160 pages.
    - NETWORK - Research materials (Box 188, Folder 8)
      Marked "'Network,' Research prepared for Larry Gelbart, by Bobette Buster, January 1996."
    - NIRVANA WEST - Writers Guild West registration of story idea and title for a television series (Box 164, Folder 10)
      With typed and handwritten description of the proposed series. April 14, 1977.
    - NOAH - Treatment for television project (Box 81, Folder 13)
      Written by Larry Gelbart and Leonard Gross. 6 p.
    - NOSTALGIA - Scripts (Box 189, Folder 8)
      2 copies. Draft, signed "Larry", October 1967, annotated, 15 p. Written for Jimmy Durante.
    - OPEN END, WITH DAVID SUSSKIND - Transcript of Interview program on Channel 13-WNTA (Box 155, Folder 6)
      Guests Charles Andrews, Sheldon Keller, Larry Gelbart, Jack Douglas, Mel Brooks, and Mel Tolkin, 51 pages. Air date 02/14/60.
    - OPENING NIGHT - Incomplete script with jokes. (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - OPENING NIGHT - First draft script and promotional sheet (Box 81, Folder 12)
      First draft script, n.d., 71+ pages. Staring Lucille Ball, Jack Benny, Andy Griffith, Garry Moore & Danny Thomas. - Fan letter, 10/10/62, 1 p.
    - PRESIDENT IS MELTING (THE) - Notes for HBO meeting (Box 61, Folder 6)
      10/8/96, 5p. Treatment by Gelbart, Markowitz, Boiteau & Stansfield, 10p (2copie). Treatment, 10/28/96, 9p. Treatment, 10/30/96, 11p. Treatment, 2p (2). Sample pages of script, 11/19/96, 2p. Correspondence, approx. 10 items.
    - PUT THEM ALL TOGETHER - Scripts by Larry Gelbart. (Box 150, Folder 5)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten first draft, 03/01/73, 25+ p. - Typed first draft, same date, 25 p.
    - REMEMBER MONA FAYE? - Script by Larry Gelbart. (Box 153, Folder 1)
      Draft, no date, 31 p. - Revision pages, no date, 11 p.
    - ROLL OUT! - PAPER CAPER, THE (Box 40, Folder 1)
      Scripts by Simon Muntner dated September, 21 and October 12, 1973, both annotated. - Television [budget] estimate for 22 episodes.
    - ROLL OUT! - SUNDAY, SWETT SUNDAY (Box 40, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller, story by Gene Reynolds, July 30 and August 14, 1973 (2 copies), all with annotations. - Handwritten draft and additional pages of changes.
    - ROLL OUT! - STRANGE BEDFELLOWS (Box 40, Folder 3)
      Scripts by John Boni and Thad Mumford, dated 10/18/73. 2 copies, one with added scenes.
    - ROLL OUT! - SWEET MILLION (Box 40, Folder 4)
      Scripts by Howard Merril, revised final, dated September 26, 1973. and undated revised script with annotations.
    - ROLL OUT! - HONOR TRUCK (Box 91, Folder 4)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart & Sheldon Keller. Rev final, 08/31/73, annotated, 37 p. - Final, 07/23/73, annotated, 37 p. - Rev. final, August 1973, annotated. - Revised pages, annotated, n.d.
    - ROLL OUT! - MEMBERS OF THE WEDDING (Box 91, Folder 5)
      Scripts by David P. Lewis, Booker Bradshaw, Larry Gelbart, & Sheldon Keller. - Rev final, 10/01/73, annotated, 40 p. - Rev final, 10/01/73, 35 p.
    - ROLL OUT! - NO WAGES-ALL FEAR (Box 91, Folder 6)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart, Sheldon Keller, and Gene Reynolds. - Final draft, 08/20/73, annotated, 33 p. - Final draft, Typed, 08/20/73, annotated, 41 p.
    - ROLL OUT! - DIDN'T HE RAMBLE (Box 91, Folder 7)
      Scripts by Sid Dorfman. Final, 08/17/73, annotated, 31 p. - Draft, n.d., annotated, 46 p.
    - ROLL OUT! - Pilot (Box 91, Folder 8)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart. First draft, typed, 09/05/72, annotated, 34 p. - Draft, annotated, n.d., 36 p.
    - ROLL OUT! - DARK VICTORY (Box 91, Folder 9)
      Script by Peter Meyerson. - Final Draft, dated 10/04/73, 38 p.
    - ROLL OUT! - BLUES FOR B.J. (Box 91, Folder 10)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart, Sheldon Keller, & Gene Reynolds. -Rev final, 08/14/73, annotated, 33 p. - Rev final, 08/14/73, annotated, 36 p. - Typed draft, annotated, n.d., 43 p.
    - ROLL OUT! - CHRISTMAS OF '44 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      Script by Larry Gelbart, Sheldon Keller, & Sid Dorfman. Final, 10/24/73, 38 p.
    - ROLL OUT! - DEAR ROCCO (Box 92, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Rick Mittleman. Final, 08/30/73, 80 p. - Final, 08/21/73, annotated, 43 p. - Partial draft, 09/14/73, annotated, pp. 13-39.
    - RUNNING WILDE - Correspondence between Gary Markowitz and Larry Gelbart regarding production and revisions to scripts (Box 143, Folder 11)
      1991
    - RUNNING WILDE - MOTEL PARADISO (Box 144, Folder 1)
      Script by Larry Gelbart and Gary Markowitz. Rev. 12/04/91, 31 p. - First draft, 10/29/91, 37 p. - Draft, no date, annotated, 30 p.
    - RUNNING WILDE - PEARBLOSSOM HIGHWAY (Box 144, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Gary Markowitz and Larry Gelbart. Rev. 09/24/92, 64 p. - Draft, no date, annotated, 59 p.
    - RUNNING WILDE - Pilot (Box 144, Folder 3)
      Scripts by Gary Markowitz. Final Draft, 03/23/92, annotated, 33 p. - Final draft, 10/08/92, 33 p.
    - RUNNING WILDE - MAN WHO LOVED CARS, THE (Box 144, Folder 4)
      Scripts by Gary Markowitz. Final draft, 03/23/92, 30.
    - RUNNING WILDE - CHARIOT OF THE GODS (Box 144, Folder 5)
      Script by Gary Markowitz. Second draft, 11/26/91, 31 p.
    - RUNNING WILDE - Correspondence with NBC (Box 144, Folder 6)
      October 1991.
    - SID CAESAR INVITES YOU - Show #1A-2A (Box 22, Folder 8)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart, Neil Simon and Mike Stewart. 01/26/58 - 01/21/58.
    - STARTIME - Pilot (Box 90, Folder 6)
      Scripts. No author. titled: "Wonderfulful World of Entertainment". Draft, 9/9/59. 65 p. - Revised, 09/17/59, annotated, 82 p. - Revised, 9/20/59, 85 p. - Final, 9/22/59, 85 p.
    - TEXACO COMMAND APPEARANCE - Script (Box 132, Folder 4)
      American Theater Wing Presents: Texaco Command Appearance, September 19, 1957, Honoring Ed Wynn. Program, final rev. 09/16/57.
    - THE ALL STAR REVIEW - GEORGE JESSEL SHOW, THE (Box 167, Folder 3)
      Script. No author, draft marked "Revised 9/5/52, annotated, 45+ pages.
    - THE CHEVROLET GOLDEN ANNIVERSARY SHOW - Scripts (Box 23, Folder 5)
      Air date November 3, 1961, 77 pages and 85 pages. Writers: Larry Gelbart and Gary Belkin. Includes rehearsal schedule, and several pages of revisions.
    - THE CHEVROLET GOLDEN ANNIVERSARY SHOW - Scripts (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Air date November 3, 1961, 85 pages w/revisions inserted. - Several pages of revisions.
    - THE CHEVY SHOW - Script final (Box 24, Folder 1)
      November 2, 1958. Signed by Larry Gelbart.
    - THE DANNY KAYE SHOW - PRIMER (Box 151, Folder 8)
      Typed notes for episode, 8 p. - Handwritten version. 2 items.
    - THE DANNY KAYE SHOW - Pilot (Box 151, Folder 9)
      Script by Mel Tolkin, Sheldon Keller, Herbert Baker, Sual Ilson, Ernest Chambers, and Larry Gelbart. - Draft, 08/10/63, 44 p.
    - THE DANNY KAYE SHOW - Episode # 2 (Box 151, Folder 10)
      Script by Herbert Baker, Mel Tolkin, Sheldon Keller, Saul Ilson, Ernest Chambers, and Larry Gelbart. Draft, 08/17/63, 71 p.
    - THE HOUSE THAT JACK BUILT - Scripts for pilot episode written by Larry Gelbart. (Box 43, Folder 6)
      Item 1: First draft, dated 12/19/72. Item 2: date 12/28/72.
    - THE HOUSE THAT JACK BUILT - Pilot (Box 45, Folder 2)
      Handwritten draft, n.d. - Drafts dated December 18 and 28, 1972, typed and ms. - "Sample story lines" by Gene Reynolds and Larry Gelbart, 04/14/74 and 03/07/74 (2 copies). - "Notes", 5 pages.
    - THE LARRY STORCH SHOW - Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Marvin Fisher (Box 132, Folder 5)
      Draft, no date, annotated. -Two revised. drafts, May 20 (no year).
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode # 1 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      Scripts. Rehearsal, Camera, UK Transmission, US Transmission. Written by Chris Allen, Barry Levinson, John Antrobus, et al, supervised by Larry Gelbart. Dated March 1971.
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode # 2 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      Scripts: Rehearsal, Camera, UK Transmission, US Transmission. Written by Chris Allen, Larry Gelbart, John Antrobus, et al. Dated June 1971.
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode # 3 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      Scripts: Rehearsal, Camera, UK Transmission, US Transmission. Written by Chris Allen, Larry Gelbart, and John Antrobus, et al. Dated July, 1971.
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode # 4 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      Scripts: Draft, Rehearsal, Camera, UK Transmission, US Transmission. Written by Chris Allen, Larry Gelbart, John Antrobus, et al. Dated July, 1971.
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode # 5 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      Scripts: Draft, Rehearsal, Camera, UK Transmission, US Transmission. Written by Chris Allen, Larry Gelbart, Ruby De Luca, et al. Dated July 1971.
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode # 6 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      Scripts: Draft, Rehearsal, Camera, UK Transmission, US Transmission. Written by Chris Allen, Larry Gelbart, Rudy de Luca, et al. Dated July, 1971.
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode # 7 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      Scripts: Draft, Rehearsal, Amended Rehearsal, Camera, UK Transmission, US Transmission. Written by Chris Allen, Larry Gelbart, Rudy de Luca, et al. Dated August, 1971.
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode # 8 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      Scripts: Draft, Rehearsal, Camera, UK Transmission, US Transmission. Written by Chris Allen, Larry Gelbart, Rudy de Luca, et al. Dated August, 1971.
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode # 9 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode #10 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      Scripts: Draft, Rehearsal, Camera UK Transmission, US Transmission. Written by Chris Allen, Larry Gelbart, Rudy de Luca, et al. Dated September, 1971.
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode #11 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      Scripts: Draft, Rehearsal, Camera, UK Transmission, US Transmission. Written by Chris Allen, Larry Gelbart, Rudy de Luca, et al. Dated September, 1971.
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode #12 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode #13 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Episode #14 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - GOLDDIGGERS (Box 65, Folder 3)
      Scripts: Rehearsal (non-audience), Audience script. No authors. Dated June, 1970.
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Sketches and sketch ideas by Larry Gelbart et al (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Sketches by Larry Gelbart et al (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Audit of the accounts of the program (Box 66, Folder 2)
      April 1st to August 31st 1972, London.
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Production information file (Box 66, Folder 3)
      Distribution reports 12/75 to 5/82. - "Notes from meeting with Lew Grade" (14/10/70 re US show) - Contract (draft) ITC and ATV Network, (5/3/71).- Program budget. - Salary list - Production Personnel.
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Program Running Order lists for shows 1-14 (for U.S. and U.K. versions) (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - THE MARTY FELDMAN COMEDY MACHINE - Correspondence between Gelbart and Sir Lew Grade, and A. R. Lucas from ATC, et al (Box 66, Folder 5)
      November 1970 through February, 1972, approx. 40 items.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 87, Folder 4)
      Air date: 01/29/59. Guest stars Bing, Dennis, Philip, and Lindsay Crosby. Revised, 01/26/59, 28 p. - First draft, 01/14/59, 30 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 87, Folder 5)
      Air date: 02/05/59. Guest star Dinah Shore. First draft, 01/27/59, 26 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 87, Folder 6)
      Air date: 02/12/59. Guest star Andy Williams. Revised, 02/10/59, 28 p. - First draft, 02/03/59.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 87, Folder 7)
      Air date: 02/19/59. Guest stars Arthur Godfrey, Connie Francis, & Martin Block. Revised, 02/10/59, 28 p. - First draft, 02/03/59.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 87, Folder 8)
      Air date: 02/26/59. Guest star Dorothy Kirsten. Revised, 02/23/59, 27 p. - First draft, 02/18/59.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 87, Folder 9)
      Air date: 03/05/59. Guest stars The Four Lads, Frankie Avalon, and Shirley Boone. Revised, 03/02/59, 29 p. - First draft, 02/25/59, 24 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 87, Folder 10)
      Air date: 03/12/59. Guest star Maureen O'Hara. Revised, 03/10/59, 35 p. - First draft, no date, 27 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 87, Folder 11)
      Air date: 03/16/59. Guest stars Shari Leis and Eddie Bracken. Revised, 03/16/59, 35 p. - First Draft, 03/11/59, 38 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 87, Folder 12)
      Air date: 03/26/59. Guest stars Tab Hunter and Dodie Stevens. Revised, 03/23/59, 32 p. - First draft, 03/19/59, 26 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 1)
      Air date: 04/30/59. Guest Pat Suzuki. First draft, 04/06/59, 28 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 2)
      Air date: 04/16/59. Guest stars Jo Stafford, Al Caiola, Tony Mattola, and Howard Collins. First draft, 04/08/59, 24 p. - First draft, 04/09/59, 33 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 3)
      Air date: 04/23/59. Guest stars Jackie Cooper and Eddie Hodges. First draft, 04/16/59, 31 p. - First draft, n.d., 29 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 4)
      Air date: 05/14/59. Guest star Any Williams. First drafts, 04/21/59, 26 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts (Box 88, Folder 5)
      Air date: 05/28/59. From the United States Naval Academy, Annapolis, MD. First drafts, 05/02/59, 28 p. & 30.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 6)
      Air date: 06/18/59. Guest star, Gordon Macrae. First drafts, 05/18/59, 31 & 30 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 7)
      Air date: 05/28/59. Rev. draft 05/26/59, 27 p. - First draft, 05/25/59, annotated, 25 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 8)
      Air date: 06/04/59. Guest stars, The McGuire Sisters. First draft, 06/01/59, 22 p. - First draft, n.d., 23 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts (2 copies) by Larry Gelbart. (Box 88, Folder 9)
      Air date: 06/25/59 First drafts, 06/01/59, 24 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 10)
      Air date: 06/11/59. Guest star, Red Foley. First drafts, 06/08/59, 28 & 27 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 11)
      Air date: 01/01/59. Guest star Johnny Mathis. First drafts, 12/29/58, 31 & 34 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts (Box 88, Folder 12)
      Air date: 01/08/59. Guest stars Alfred Drake and the Annapolis Glee Club. First drafts, 12/30/58, 19 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 13)
      Air date: 02/05/59. Guest star Dinah Shore. First draft, 01/05/59, 27 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 14)
      Air date: 01/22/59. Guest Stars Gisele Mackenzie and Esquivel. First drafts, 01/06/59, 23 & 24 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 15)
      Air date: 01/15/59. Guest star Ginger Rogers. First drafts, 01/09/59, 23 & 24 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 16)
      Air date: 04/02/59. Guest stars Teresa Brewer and Dukes of Dixieland. First drafts: 03/26/59, 23 & 24 p.
    - THE PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM - Scripts by Larry Gelbart (Box 88, Folder 17)
      Air date: 04/09/59. Guest star David Wayne. First drafts, 03/31/59, 26 & 28 p.
    - THE PATRICE MUNSEL SHOW - October 4 1957 - January 3 1958 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart & Sheldon Keller. First draft, 10/4/57. - First draft, 10/11/57. - Draft, 10/25/57. - Draft, marked "Writers," 01/03/58.
    - THE PATRICE MUNSEL SHOW - January 10 1958 - February 7 1958 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. - Draft, 01/10/58, annotated, 15 p. - "Writers" Draft, 01/31/58, annotated, 13 p. - Draft, 02/07/58, 24 p. - Rev. draft, 02/07/58, 24 p.
    - THE PATRICE MUNSEL SHOW - February 14 - 28, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. Draft, 02/14/58. - Rev. draft, 02/21/58, annotated. - Rev. draft, 02/28/58, annotated.
    - THE PATRICE MUNSEL SHOW - January 10 & March 7-14 1958 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. "Writers" draft, 01/10/58, annotated, 26 p. - Rev. draft, 03/07/58, annotated. - Rev draft, marked "Beth," 03/14/58, annotated.
    - THE PATRICE MUNSEL SHOW - January 24 & March 7 & 21, 1958 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. Draft, 01/24/58, annotated. - Draft, 03/07/58, annotated. Draft, 03/21/58, annotated.
    - THE PATRICE MUNSEL SHOW - March 28 - April 11, 1958 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      Scripts: Draft, 03/28/58. - Rev. draft, 04/04/58, annotated. - Draft, 04/11/58, one page handwritten.
    - THE PATRICE MUNSEL SHOW - April 18 - May 2, 1958 (Box 98, Folder 3)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. Draft, 04/18/58, annotated. - Draft, labeled "New version," 04/25/58. - Draft, 05/02/58.
    - THE PATRICE MUNSEL SHOW - May 9 - 23 1958 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. Draft, 05/09/58, routine sheet handwritten. - Draft, 05/16/58, annotated. - Draft, 05/23/58, annotated.
    - THE PATRICE MUNSEL SHOW - May 30 & June 6, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. - Draft, 05/30/58. - Draft, 06/06/58, annotated.
    - THE PATRICE MUNSEL SHOW - Pilot & June 13, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. Pilot, "first copy," 10/18/57, annotated. - Draft, 06/13/58, annotated.
    - THE PATRICE MUNSEL SHOW - November 15 - 22, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. - Draft, 11/15/58, annotated. - Draft, 11/22/58.
    - THE PATRICE MUNSEL SHOW - December 13 - 27, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. - Draft, 12/13/58, annotated. - Rev. draft, 12/20/58, annotated. - Rev. draft, marked "Larry, Shelly," 12/27/58, annotated.
    - THE PHIL SILVERS SHOW - Pilot (Box 151, Folder 11)
      Scripts by Irving Pincus and Larry Gelbart. - Rev., 11/22/66, 41 p. - Rev., 11/10/66, annotated, 59 p. - Revision pages (3).
    - THE PONTIAC FOUR-IN-ONE SHOW - CYRIL RITCHARD SHOW, THE (Box 151, Folder 15)
      Script. No Author. First draft, 12/20/59, 27 p.
    - THE PONTIAC FOUR-IN-ONE-SHOW - BEATRICE LILLIE SHOW, THE (Box 151, Folder 16)
      Scripts. No author. First draft, no date, 31 p. - Final, 11/30/59, annotated, 26 p.
    - THE PONTIAC FOUR-IN-ONE-SHOW - FOUR FOR TONIGHT (Box 151, Folder 17)
      Script. No author. Revised final, air script, 02/19/60, 84 p.
    - THE RED BUTTONS SHOW - GERMAN MOVIE SKETCH (Box 81, Folder 1)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Hal Collins. Draft, air date 01/26/53, annotated, 18 p. - Draft, 18 p.
    - THE RED BUTTONS SHOW - AUTOGRAPH BOOK (Box 81, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Hal Collins. Draft, air date 01/04/54, 21 p. - Various sketches.
    - THE RED BUTTONS SHOW - MILLION DOLLAR HEIR (Box 81, Folder 3)
      Script by Larry Gelbart & Hal Collins. Draft, air date 02/09/53.
    - THE RED BUTTONS SHOW - PURSE SNATCHER, THE (Box 81, Folder 4)
      Script by Larry Gelbart & Hal Collins, et al. Draft, air date, 03/02/53, annotated, 15 p.
    - THE RED BUTTONS SHOW - STOCK BROKER SKETCH (Box 81, Folder 5)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart & Hal Collins. 2nd revision, annotated, 41 p. - Partial script, annotated, pp. 3-17. - Partial script, annotated, 23 p.
    - THE RED BUTTONS SHOW - ROCKY VERSUS SLAPSIE (Box 81, Folder 6)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart & Hal Collins, et al. - Partial draft, air date 03/23/53, annotated, 22 p. - Partial, 17 p. - Revised pages, annotated, pp. 19-20.
    - THE RED BUTTONS SHOW - DOCTOR KEEGLEFARVEN (Box 81, Folder 7)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart & Hal Collins, et al. - Revised draft, 03/30/53, annotated, 17 p. - 2nd revision, 17 p. - Revision, 14 p.
    - THE RED BUTTONS SHOW - MUGSY ON PAROLE (Box 81, Folder 8)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart & Hal Collins, et al. Draft. air date, 04/06/53, 21 p. - Revised draft, 04/03/53, annotated, 18 p. Draft, annotated, 18 p. - Revised draft, 15 p.
    - THE RED BUTTONS SHOW - ROCKY VS HONEY BOY (Box 81, Folder 9)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart & Hal Collins, et al. Draft, air date 04/27/53, annotated, 42 p. - Draft, annotated.